const quizData = [
    {
      question: "When was heavy metal music first developed?",
      options: ["early 60s", "early 70s", "early 80s", "early 90s"],
      answer: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "In which subgenre of metal do artists typically adopt pseudonyms and perform in corpse paint?",
      options: ["Black Metal", "Trash Metal", "Alternative Metal", "Folk Metal"],
      answer: 0,
    },
    {
      question: "What was the Iron Maiden’s mascot called?",
      options: ["Tom", "Leon", "Eddie", "Goku"],
      answer: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Which subgenre of heavy metal is known as hair metal?",
      options: ["Doom Metal", "Alternative Metal", "Punk", "Glam Metal"],
      answer: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "What is the favourite stage effect of Rammstein?",
      options: ["Lasers", "Fire", "Light shows", "Video projections"],
      answer: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Which American heavy metal band is known for songs like “Nightmare”, “Hail to the King”, or “Buried Alive”?",
      options: ["My Chemical Romance", "Metallica", "Iron Maiden", "Avenged Sevenfold"],
      answer: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "Which of the following is not an album by Metallica?",
      options: ["Meteora", "MetalSt. Anger", "Master of Puppets", "Reload"],
      answer: 0,
    },
    {
      question: "'Symphony of Destruction' is a song by which heavy metal band?",
      options: ["Metallica", "Slipknot", "Megadeath", "Black Sabbath"],
      answer: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "From which country does the heavy metal band Iron Maiden come from?",
      options: ["Brazil", "Germany", "Denmark", "England"],
      answer: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "Which heavy metal band has it an album called “Roots”?",
      options: ["Slipknot", "Sepultura", "Korn", "Lamb of God"],
      answer: 1,
    },
    
  ];